<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aklny</string>
    <string name="title_for_cardView_1">New!</string>
    <string name="paragraph_for_cardView_1">We got you! Round the clock Round the year</string>
    <string name="egyptian_food">Egyptian Food</string>
    <string name="algeria_food">Algerian Food</string>
    <string name="tunisia_food">Tunisian Food</string>
    <string name="Moroccan_food">Moroccan Food</string>
    <string name="koshary_EG">koshary</string>
    <string name="koshary_deatails_EG">Spray a pot with a little oil and put it on the fire.
    Add onions and garlic and saute them well.
    Put half of the onion in a plate and set aside.
    To the rest of the onion, add the rice and pour one and a half cups of water.
    Leave the mixture until it boils, then reduce the heat, cover the pot, and leave it for about 10 minutes until it is cooked.
    Add the boiled lentils and pasta, then pour one and a half cups of water.
    Season with salt, black pepper, sweet pepper and cumin, and leave the mixture on low heat for about 15 minutes.
    To prepare the sauce: Pour the tomato sauce into a saucepan and add the parsley.
    Season the mixture with paprika and hot pepper and bring it to a boil, then reduce the heat until the mixture is hot.
    Pour the rice mixture into a serving dish and put the sauce on it.
    Garnish with the rest of the onion mixture.
    </string>
    <string name="Feteer_Meshaltet_for_the_diet_EG">Feteer Meshaltet for the diet</string>
    <string name="Feteer_Meshaltet_for_the_diet_details_EG">Put the flour in a large bowl, then add the salt and water.
    Knead the mixture with your hand to get a soft, cohesive dough.
    Cut the dough into small pieces, then roll each piece with your hand.
    Brush each dough ball with oil and let it rest for 30 minutes.
    Take a ball of dough and roll it out, then brush it with butter.
    Apply the dough to each other to get a square and set it aside.
    Take a second ball, roll it out, and brush it with butter.
    Put the first square of dough inside the second dough, close it to each other in the form of a square and set it aside.
    Take a third ball, roll it out, and grease it with butter.
    Put the second dough square inside the third dough and close it together.
    Put the pie on a tray greased with oil and put it in the oven on a high temperature for about 15 minutes or until it is cooked.</string>
    <string name="Hawawshi_EG">Hawawshi</string>
    <string name="Hawawshi_details_EG">Put the chopped onions in a deep bowl and set aside, then chop the peppers into small pieces and add them on top of the onions.
    Season with salt, cumin, cardamom and black pepper.
    Add the minced meat and put a piece of lamb fat on the mixture, then stir the mixture well until the ingredients overlap and mix with each other, then put the bowl into the refrigerator for about an hour.
    After the time has passed, bring the bread and make a small hole on the side of each loaf, insert the filling and spread it inside the loaf, then repeat the process until the quantity runs out.
    Grease the bread with oil from the top and bottom.
    Preheat the oven to 180 degrees Celsius, then spread the bread in an oven tray and arrange it well and put it in the oven for 20 minutes until it is done, then serve.
    </string>
    <string name="Egyptian_Fattah_Cups_EG">Egyptian Fattah Cups</string>
    <string name="Egyptian_Fattah_Cups_details_EG">To boil the meat: Saute the meat in ghee with mastic and the spice mixture consisting of (cardamom, bay leaf, mastic and cinnamon), add vegetables and water and leave it to simmer for an hour and a half or two hours, depending on the type of meat used.
    Grease the bread with ghee and put it in cupcake cups and put it in the oven until it turns golden.
    To prepare the sauce: Fry the garlic in the oil, add vinegar and a little meat broth, and after boiling, divide the quantity in half. The first part we leave it in the pot, and the second part of the broth we put it in a cup on the side.
    Add tomato juice and tomato paste to the sauce ingredients in the pot and bring to a boil.
    We start by filling the cups of toasted bread with rice, adding a little vinegar broth, a little toasted bread, adding a second layer of rice, then adding the sauce and meat broth on top.
    Serve the fattah hot.</string>
    <string name="Muammar_rice_EG">Muammar_rice</string>
    <string name="Muammar_rice_Details_EG">Start by soaking the rice in a quantity of lukewarm water for 15 minutes, then wash it and drain it well from the water.
    Preheat the oven to 200 degrees Celsius and grease a casserole, deep pot or Pyrex tray with a little butter.
    Fry the chopped onion in a little oil, then add a small amount of pepper, salt and cinnamon until it wilts and turns golden.
    Pour the rice over the onion mixture and stir well, then pour the entire mixture into the tajine or special saucepan.
    Mix the milk, cream and butter in a saucepan and then put it on the fire for a few minutes until it starts to boil, stirring slowly constantly.
    Pour the milk mixture over the rice in the casserole, then cover it well with tin foil and place it inside the preheated oven after lowering the temperature to 180°C until the casserole is cooked and the liquid dries up and the rice is completely absorbed for 30-45 minutes.
    Take the casserole out of the oven, then remove the tin, then return it to the oven to turn red and golden for 10 minutes only.
    Serve the casserole hot after garnishing its surface with a little ground cinnamon.</string>
    <string name="Hamaam_Mahshiun_EG">Hamaam Mahshiun</string>
    <string name="Hamaam_Mahshiun_details_EG">Clean the pigeons well, and keep the giblets and liver and cut them into cubes, and put them in a bowl.
    Melt the ghee in a saucepan over a medium heat, add the onions and mastic, and stir until the onions wilt.
     Add the giblets and liver, and stir until the liquids have evaporated.
    Add the bay leaf, and flavor with black pepper, Arabic spices, cinnamon and cardamom, and stir until the ingredients overlap.
     Add the grits, season with salt and stir until the ingredients are combined.
    Add the boiling water, stir the ingredients until they overlap, and leave the mixture on the fire until the freekeh is half cooked, then remove it from the heat.
     Stuff the pigeons with the grits mixture and tie the legs with cooking thread.
    Put a large amount of water in a saucepan over a medium heat, and add the carrots, onions, salt and black pepper.
     When the mixture boils, add the stuffed pigeon, and boil the pigeon for an hour until it is cooked.
    Preheat the oven to 180 degrees Celsius and grease an oven tray with a little vegetable oil.
     Put the pigeons on the oven tray and put them in the oven until they are browned.
     Serve the dish hot.</string>
    <string name="Moussaka_EG">Moussaka</string>
    <string name="Moussaka_details_EG">Put onions, tomatoes and garlic.
    Fry potatoes, eggplant and carrots in oil.
    Then we mix them together and serve the dish.</string>
    <string name="Al_Tameya">Al_Tameya</string>
    <string name="Al_Tameya_details">In a food processor, put the peeled beans, onions, garlic, parsley and coriander, then mash the ingredients well.
    Distribute the mixture in a medium sized bowl.
    Season with salt, red pepper, dry coriander, cumin and black pepper, then mix the ingredients until you get a homogeneous mixture.
    Heat a large amount of oil in a saucepan over the fire, form the falafel mixture into small balls, then lower them into the oil and leave them until they are cooked and browned.
    Remove the falafel from the oil, place it on paper towels to absorb the excess oil, and then serve hot.</string>
    <string name="cabbage_EG">cabbage</string>
    <string name="cabbage_details_EG">In a food processor, put the peeled beans, onion, garlic, parsley and coriander and mash well.
    Distribute the mixture into a medium sized bowl.
    Season with salt, red pepper, dry coriander, cumin and black pepper, then mix, mixture until you get a homogeneous mixture.
    Heat a large amount of oil in a frying pan, shape the falafel mixture into small balls, then lower them into the oil and leave them until they are cooked and browned.
    Remove the falafel from the oil, place it on paper towels to absorb the excess oil, and then serve hot.</string>
    <string name="alraqaq_bialluhmat_almafruma_EG">alraqaq bialluhmat almafruma</string>
    <string name="alraqaq_bialluhmat_almafruma_details_EG">
        In a frying pan on the fire, heat the oil, then add the onion and stir until it wilts, add the green pepper and my heart for two minutes.
    Add the meat and my heart until it changes color, then add salt, black pepper, spices and nutmeg, and stir for two minutes.
    Cover the pan and leave the meat on a low heat until the meat is cooked and the liquids dry, stirring occasionally.
    Heat the oven at 180 degrees.Grease an oven tray with melted butter, then dip the parchment paper in the broth for one second, then place it in the tray.
    Grease the paper from the top with butter, then dip the second paper, then put it in the tray and grease it with butter.
    Repeat these steps with half the amount of tortillas, then spread the meat over the last leaf.
    Dip the first sheet of the rest of the tortillas, then place it in the tray over the meat, then brush it with butter.
    Repeat these steps with the rest of the tortillas, then brush the face with butter.
    Then cut the tortillas into triangles, then put the tray in the oven for 30 minutes, until golden.</string>

    //tusian foods
    <string name="Masmota_salad_TU">Masmota_salad</string>
    <string name="Masmota_salad_details_TU">Put the potatoes, carrots and peas on a medium heat, then pour some water until it covers the vegetables.
    Add salt and turmeric, leave the water to boil, then cover the pot, and leave it on low heat for 25 minutes until the vegetables are tender.
    Drain the vegetables from the water, let them cool completely, then add the parsley, olives, tuna, eggs, oil and black pepper, and stir well.
    Serve the masmouta salad for dinner withbread, or as an appetizer with the main lunch.</string>
    <string name="the_break_TU">The Break</string>
    <string name="the_break_details_TU">Brik is one of the basics of the Tunisian Ramadan meal, as nothing compares to a boiled crunchy stuffed with a mixture of parsley, onions and cheese and “sprayed” with black pepper, topped with an egg, topped with tuna and adults.</string>
    <string name="Omelettes_in_the_mercury_TU">Omelettes in the mercury</string>
    <string name="Omelettes_in_the_mercury_details_TU">The name of the omelette is a strange name, and it is based mainly on scrambled eggs. However, the Tunisians added the eggs to the omelette, so that the omelette in the merguez was among the list of the best popular foods, a delicious dish that bears in its taste a distinctive Tunisian character.</string>
    <string name="Frecasian_TU">Frecasian</string>
    <string name="Frecasian_details_TU">Fry the potatoes in plenty of oil, until they turn golden, then remove them from the oil, and set them aside.
    In a large bowl, cut the chicken into thin and small slices.
    Add the fried potatoes, onions, parsley, turmeric, coriander, caraway, salt and black pepper, and stir well.
    Add cheese and boiled eggs, then add eggs, and mix well.
    Grease a Pyrex tray with oil, then pour the mixture into the tray.
    Preheat the oven at 200 ° C for 30 minutes.Place the tray in the oven for 30 minutes, until the tagine is done, then serve hot.</string>
    <string name="Tunisian_tagine_with_chicken_TU">Tunisian tagine with chicken</string>
    <string name="Tunisian_tagine_with_chicken_details_TU">Fry the potatoes in plenty of oil, until they turn golden, then remove them from the oil, and set them aside.
    In a large bowl, cut the chicken into thin and small slices.
    Add the fried potatoes, onions, parsley, turmeric, coriander, caraway, salt and black pepper, and stir well.
    Add cheese and boiled eggs, then add eggs, and mix well.
    Grease a Pyrex tray with oil, then pour the mixture into the tray.</string>
    <string name="Fried_crovet_TU">Fried crovet</string>
    <string name="Fried_crovet_details_TU">Clean the amount of croft well, peel and wash well with water.
    Drain the crovite well from the wash water.
    Season the croutons with the mashed garlic, lemon juice, salt and spices, and leave for an hour.
    Stir the crovettes with the flour, then the eggs, and finally the breadcrumbs, and fry the crovettes in hot oil until golden.
    </string>
    <string name="Eggplant_salad_TU">Eggplant salad</string>
    <string name="Eggplant_salad_details_TU">Wash the eggplant well, get rid of its head, empty its ingredients, and season with salt, pepper and olive oil. Then, it is placed in the oven on a medium heat for 12 minutes. Then, set aside.
    Cut the onions and tomatoes into small pieces, and chop the parsley. Mix these greens with a mixture of lemon, olive oil, salt and pepper. The eggplant is stuffed with this mixture.
    To prepare the dates: Boil the grape juice, then leave to cool. The outer shell of the dates is removed, then these kernels are soaked in grape juice for 4 hours. Arrange in a serving dish, and decorate the center with goat cheese.</string>

    //ALGERIAN
    <string name="couscous_ALG">couscous</string>
    <string name="couscous_details_ALG">Couscous is famous for being one of the pottery dishes, that is, it is cooked in couscous pots made of pottery decorated with wonderful drawings.</string>
    <string name="percox_ALG">percox</string>
    <string name="percox_details_ALG">The broccoli is one of the most delicious Algerian dishes and it consists of various types of meat with cubes of delicious vegetables such as carrots, turnips, and tomato paste. The spices and spices that are famous for the Maghreb are added to give it a delicious flavor.
    The Algerian dish is called garlic due to its use of large quantities of garlic, and the reason for this is its multiple benefits in addition to giving it a distinctive flavor to food.
    Garlic is made by slicing the meat into medium-sized pieces. This delicious Algerian dish is served with a delicious salad flavored with the wonderful flavors of spices.</string>
    <string name="Tagen_ALG">Tagen</string>
    <string name="Tagen_details_ALG">The tagine is one of the most popular dishes in Algeria, and the entire Maghreb; It consists of vegetables, meat, as well as dry fruits and has multiple types such as olive tagine, pear tagine, seafood tagine, and meat tagine.</string>
    <string name="nerves_ALG">nerves</string>
    <string name="nerves_details_ALG">Algerians do not dispense with the asaban dish on the blessed Eid al-Adha, as it is one of the manifestations of the celebration of the feast in Algeria, as well as Tunisia, Libya and of course Egypt, but it has another name, which is Mambar.
    The nerves are prepared from the intestines of cows, sheep and camels and are stuffed with fillings of vegetables such as eggplant, potatoes, fish, rice, bacon, or couscous.</string>
    <string name="alzalabih_ALG">alzalabih</string>
    <string name="alzalabih_details_ALG">A simple oriental dessert, but very delicious. The Arab community in general is famous for it, but Algeria prepares it with a special flavour. It consists of sugar, starch and flour and fried in abundant oil. It is placed in syrup consisting of water, lemon and vanilla with sugar. It is one of the sweets that are used on occasions to welcome guests.</string>
    <string name="Sable_ajwa_ALG">Sable ajwa</string>
    <string name="Sable_ajwa_details_ALG">One of the types of Algerian sweets, consisting of a mixture of semolina and flour, which is kneaded and fried in abundant oil, then watered with the syrup previously composed of water, lemon, sugar and fragrant vanilla; Which gives it a wonderful flavor and makes it delicious and soft.</string>
    <string name="bread_in_Algeria_ALG">bread in Algeria</string>
    <string name="bread_in_Algeria_details_ALG">One of the most famous Algerian baked goods; It is a mixture of flour and water, resulting in a thin loaf called veiled and stuffed with tomatoes and onions, and prepared in the form of square layers of dough, folded several times and then fried.</string>
    <string name="Freekeh_soup_ALG">Freekeh soup</string>
    <string name="Freekeh_soup_details_ALG">Freekeh soup is one of the most delicious foods in Algeria, as it is a delicious and creamy dish because it contains pieces of meat mixed with fresh chopped coriander with pepper, onions and garlic, of course, and the main ingredient in it is freekeh.</string>
</resources>